

## Almir Hrštić

O Home: 38173, Sickte, Germany

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/almir-hrstic

**Gender:** Male **Date of birth:** 26/03/1995 **Nationality:** Bosnian-Herzegovinian

### **ABOUT ME**

I officially began my journey in 2016 when I enrolled in a technical university, acquiring theoretical knowledge. Meanwhile, I embarked on a student internship, which provided me with practical experience. Later, I transitioned into full-time work, taking on numerous responsibilities. Fast-forward to the present day, I have relocated to Germany and am exploring new opportunities. Specializing in front-end development and WordPress, I bring proficiency in back-end as well. I am always enthusiastic about learning new technologies, beyond a specific focus area.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

[ 09/2010 - 05/2014 ] **Technician** 

Co-educational High School "Hasan Kikić" msshkg.co.ba

City: Gradačac

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina Field(s) of study: Electrical Engineering

[ 09/2016 - 05/2020 ]

## **Bachelor Engineer**

American University in Bosnia and Herzegovina aubih.edu

Citv: Tuzla

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

Field(s) of study: Information Technology

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

[09/2018 - 05/2019]

## **Front-end Developer**

StarNet starnet.co.ba

City: Tuzla

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

Internship, part-time and in a remote environment. Integrated segments of a Bootstrap theme using Aurelia framework for enhanced reusability.

# [ 09/2019 – 05/2020 ] **Full-stack Developer**

Leftor leftor.com

City: Tuzla

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

Internship, part-time and in a hybrid environment. Established IMS and CAS as in-house solutions using React, Bootstrap and Laravel frameworks.

# [ 09/2020 - 08/2023 ] Front-end / WordPress Developer

Imel imel.ba

City: Lukavac

Country: Bosnia and Herzegovina

Full-time and in a hybrid environment. Developed custom-tailored solutions via

WordPress platform and various client-side technologies.

[ 09/2023 – Current ] Relocation

Career Break sickte.de

City: Sickte

**Country:** Germany

Sickte in Lower Saxony, Germany. Decided to move forward, stepping into a new chapter

of my life and actively seeking new opportunities.

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Bosnian

Other language(s):

## **English**

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1** 

### German

LISTENING A1 READING A1 WRITING A1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A1** 

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user